

## **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

C/C++, C#, JavaScript, Python and Dart Unity Godot

Git Neo4J

Agile OpenGL

STL containers

Adobe Photoshop

Office package

3DS Max

#### CONTACT

christian.martinez.de.la.rosa.99@gmail.com



https://t.me/christt105

## SOCIAL

christt105

in christianmartinezdelarosa

# CHRISTIAN MARTÍNEZ DE LA ROSA

PROGRAMMER

#### **ABOUT**

I am a dedicated programmer with a passion for creating games and tools. Since I began programming in 2017, I have developed several games and tools from scratch. My experience includes developing tools such as a  $\underline{3D}$  game engine with an integrated Lua scripting system and a  $\underline{3D}$  tile-based map editor. Additionally, I have extensive experience in Unity and C#. For more information, please visit my website at  $\underline{christt105}.\underline{github.io}$ .

## WORK EXPERIENCE

UNITY 3D DEVELOPER

Nurogames GmbH | August 2021 - Present

- Developer of <u>Ashvin</u> and <u>PRECEPT</u> WebGL platforms European Union's Horizon 2020
- Architectural 3D Simulators

UNITY DEVELOPER

Learny Land | February 2021 - July 2021

- Creation of educational apps with Unity for Android and IOS
- Worked in Code Land -Coding for Kids

## **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN VIDEO GAME DESIGN AND DEVELOPMENT CITM-UPC | 2017 - 2021

TECHNOLOGICAL BACCALAURATE
INS Bruguers, Gavà | 2015 - 2017

#### AWARDS

Honors in Bachelor subject "Project 2" as a team leader

Honors in Bachelor subject "Artificial Intelligence"